vrxstudios.com 2006-06-22

# Privacy Statement - VRX Studios

"VRX's new Hotel Program will not only help us showcase our resorts using today's highest quality, user-friendly, interactive content but it has also become a critical component of our online distribution and marketing strategy."

Randy Russell  
Senior Vice President  
**Couples Resorts**

|  | 

## VRX's PRIVACY COMMITMENT

VRX's Commitment to Privacy  
VRX Studios Inc. Inc. (VRX) is committed to protecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. VRX will continue to review and revise its policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information to better protect individuals' privacy. This may result in changes to VRX policy from time to time. 

In the course of its commercial activities and, in particular, when providing services to its clients, VRX collects personal information about its clients. 

VRX's privacy principles only apply to personal information about identifiable individuals but does not include the name, title, business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization, or anonymous or aggregated information. In the context of this policy, the term "clients" includes all current, former and prospective clients.

Why does VRX Collect Personal Information?   
VRX may use personal information to provide business services; for billing, record-keeping and other client contact and service matters; for audit and record-keeping purposes; for account collection purposes; to manage and develop its business and operations; to learn about the needs of current and potential clients, to develop or offer services and products tailored to those needs and to communicate with those clients regarding current and future products and services; and to follow up on client comments and suggestions. 

In the normal course of business, VRX does not share or sell any personally identifiable information to third parties. VRX may however share information in an anonymous aggregate form, among its affiliates.

Collection of Personal Information  
VRX collects, uses and discloses personal information only for the purposes that a reasonable person would consider appropriate - and only by lawful and fair means. Whenever possible, VRX collects personal information about clients and other individuals directly from those parties or through referrals by persons whom such parties have requested to provide us with such information.

Disclosure of Personal Information  
VRX will only disclose personal information for the purposes related to providing services, or with a person's express consent, or otherwise if required or authorized by law. For example, VRX may disclose a person's information when the business services that VRX provides to that person require VRX to give the personal information to third parties; where it is necessary to establish or collect fees; if VRX engages third party service providers on the client's behalf, including data processing or accounting; or if a court issues a sub-poena. 

Consent  
We may obtain personal consent to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information either expressly, for stated purposes or impliedly when the purposes are not stated expressly but are indicated by the relevant circumstances or follow logically from other expressly stated purposes. A person may withdraw or amend any consent previously given by contacting VRX's Privacy Officer, subject to any legal or contractual restrictions and upon reasonable notice to VRX. 

A person's consent to collect certain personal information may be required in order for VRX to provide business services. However, as a condition of providing a service VRX will not require that personal information not related to providing such service be provided.

Updating Personal Information  
Because VRX uses personal information to provide business services to clients or make decisions related to employment, it is important that personal information be accurate and up-to-date. 

If any of your information changes, please inform us so that we can make any necessary changes. 

Safety of Personal Information  
VRX uses appropriate security measures to protect against loss, theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, use or modification of personal information. Such measures will vary depending on the sensitivity, amount, format, nature and storage of the personal information and will involve physical, organizational and electronic security measures. 

VRX may occasionally transfer personal information to trusted third-party providers. VRX requires that these third-party service providers offer a level of security that meets the standards established by VRX.

Access to Personal Information  
VRX will respond promptly to any request for access to personal information. There will be no cost for reasonable requests to such access, unless one requests copies of records, or when retrieval costs are excessive. VRX will advise of the cost, if any, prior to the retrieval of such records or information. VRX will not respond to requests for access to personal information where it is not required by law to do so, including frivolous or vexatious requests. 

In certain circumstances, VRX may be unable to provide access to some or all of the personal information that it holds about a person. Such circumstances include those in which the personal information cannot be separated from the records of others, cannot be disclosed for reasons of personal security or commercial confidentiality (including, in relation to VRX) or is protected by professional standards relating to confidentiality or solicitor-client privilege. 

Correcting Errors  
If VRX holds information that is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date, VRX will take appropriate steps to correct it upon notification, where permitted or required by law.

Website  
The VRX website may contain links to other sites, which are not governed by the privacy policy of VRX. VRX may monitor traffic patterns, site usage and related site information in order to optimize its web service. VRX may provide aggregated information to third parties, but these statistics do not include any identifiable personal information. 

Questions, Concerns, Requests for Access  
For questions relating to this notice, to access personal information or to change preferences regarding our use of registered users' information, please contact VRX's Privacy Officer at 1.604.687.8032 or use this form.
